A Guide to the John S. and James L. Knight Foundation records, Audiovisual Materials, RG 7 FA1801
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Photographs, 1890-2019; 5; 5.08 Cubic Feet 12 containers
  - Events, 1993-2012; 2; 1.14 Cubic Feet 3 letter document boxes
    - Ceremony Honoring W. Gerald Austen, Akron, OH - Low Res Photos (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Knight Arts Awards Ceremony, 2009 November 30 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      Knight File Number - 4671
      Ceremony, at the Arsht Center in Miami, honored the 2009 winners of the Knight Arts contest in Miami. Includes cd, thumbnail photos and some names of participants.
    - Knight Arts Awards Ceremony - High Res Files (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Trustees at Knight Concert Hall, 2012 June 6 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      Knight File Number - 5877
      Reviewing plans for the John S. and James L. Knight Concert Hall are Rob Briggs and Mariam Noland (in hard hats) and Alberto Ibarguen.
  - History, 1930-1969; 3; 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
    - Akron Beacon Journal photos, c. 1930s (Box 1, Folder 15)
      Knight File Number - 1870
      Photo of Akron Beacon Journal newsboys (1930s?) and of the offices and press rooms (15 items on 1 cd) from the University of Akron archives.
    - Akron Beacon Journal photos - University of Akron Collection (15 photos), c. 1930s (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Miami Herald Press Room, c. 1940-1949 (Box 1, Folder 16)
      Knight File Number - 2466
      Six images (copies) of the Miami Herald's press room operations.
    - Miami Herald, 1941 November 16 (Box 1, Folder 17)
      Knight File Number - 1864
      Autographed photo of C. Blake McDowell and Smith Davis taken at time of dedication of Miami Herald building.
    - Knight Ridder, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 18)
      Knight File Number - 1869
      Knight Ridder banquet (attendees include Lee and Tina Hills, Creed Black, Jim Batten, Larry Jinks, etc.)
  - People, 1890-2019; 4; 3.18 Cubic Feet 7 containers
    - Advisors, 1993-1998, undated; 1
      - Chandler, John W., undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
        Knight File Number - 2810
        Photograph, b/w, of John W. Chandler, Chairman, Knight Foundation Advisory Committee.
      - Fielder, Virginia Dodge, undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
        Knight File Number - 2811
        Photograph, b/w, of Virginia Dodge Fielder, Journalism Advisory Committee.
      - Gilman, Richard, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 32)
        Knight File Number - 2199
        Contact sheet and one 8"x10" photograph of Richard Gilman, former advisor on the Excellence in Education program to the Knight Foundation. Black and white.
      - Osborne, Burl, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 35)
        Knight File Number - 2200
        Photographs of Burl Osborne, former member of the Knight Foundation Journalism Advisory Committee (retired 1998). Black & white photos (one 8"x10", multiple 5"x7" copies of the same image) and the negative.
      - Owens, Lewis, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 36)
        Knight File Number - 2201
        Photograph of Lewis Owens, formerly community advisor for Lexington, Kentucky to the Knight Foundation. Black & white photo, 5"x7".
      - Wald, Richard, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 37)
        Knight File Number - 2202
        Photographs of Richard Wald, former member of the Journalism Advisory Committlee, who retired in 1998. Includes two color portraits (8x10, 5x7) and a negative.
    - Knight Chairholders, 1991-1996; 2
      - Alves, Rosental Calmon, 1996 January 16 (Box 1, Folder 23)
        Knight File Number - 911
        Photographs of Rosental Calmon Alves, holder of the Knight Chair at the University of Texas as of 1/16/96. Includes photos of Alves teaching, talking with students, and portraits. Black & white and color. Some negatives included.
      - Broder, David, 1993 December (Box 1, Folder 24)
        Knight File Number - 916
        Photograph of David Broder, holder of the Knight Chair at Duke University, 1993. Black & white.
      - Doig, Stephen K., 1996 June (Box 1, Folder 25)
        Knight File Number - 921
        Photograph of Stephen K. Doig, holder of Knight Chair in Computer-Assisted Journalism at Arizona State University. Black & white.
      - Ginn, John, 1991 June (Box 1, Folder 26)
        Knight File Number - 924
        Photographs of John Ginn, holder of the Knight Chair at the University of Kansas, ca. 1991. Black & white. Negative
      - Raspberry, William, 1995 June (Box 1, Folder 27)
        Knight File Number - 937
        Photographs of William Raspberry, holder of the Knight Chair at Duke University, 1995. Photo by the Washington Post. Black & white.
      - Ritchie, Joseph, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 28)
        Knight File Number - 938
        Photograph of Joseph E. Ritchie, holder of the Knight Chair at the Florida Agricultural and Mechanical University, 1992. Black & white.
    - Knight Family, 1890-1985; 3
      - Copies of Knight Historical Photographs, c. 1920-1990 (Box 1, Folder 3-5)
        Knight File Number - 4409
        Three folders of copies of Knight Historical photographs, many of which were used in the John S. Knight biography: 1) Knight family 2) Knight brothers (some in groups) 3) Knight trustees
      - Knight, Charles Landon, 1907 June 5 (Box 1, Folder 1)
        Knight File Number - 2282
        Photos of Charles Landon Knight, father of the Knight brothers. Consists of one b&w image of Charles with his wife Clara in Atlantic City, June 5, 1907 and three undated photos (b&w) taken at a later age, two showing him with pipe.
      - Knight, Clara I., c. 1890-1909 (Box 1, Folder 2)
        Knight File Number - 951
        Three undated photograph of Clara I. Knight, mother of John S. and James L. Knight. Includes two portraits, ca. 1890s-1900s (one taken in Atlantic City.) (See portraits, Knight, C.L. for a portrait of Mr. and Mrs. Charles L. Knight taken in Atlantic City). Black & white. One undated color photograph signed in the back "Aunt Clara Knight" with two letters from Mary Ellen Hunter, friend of the Knight Family explaining the relationship between the Knight and Hunter family.
      - Knight Brothers (John S. and James L. Knight), 1938-1973 (Box 1, Folder 3)
        Knight File Number - 2284
        Eleven b&w and color photos of the Knight brothers: 1) JS & JL at a black-tie dinner, with CC Gibson and Tina Hills; 2) Knight papers go public, NYSE, JS & JL with Lee Hills, 1969; 3) JS & JL (wearing straw hats) at the dedication of the James L. Knight International Center, University of Miami; 4) JS & JL with Blake McDowell, holding silver plate, at 75th Dinner; 5) JS & JL in front of new Miami Herald Building, Miami, 4/1963; JS & JL, with group of friends in Akron; 6) JS & JL in press room (includes negative & copies (5x3); 7) JS & JL (in black tie) in front of a picture of a Knight; 8) JS & JL, with JS's son, Landon; 9) JS & JL, with Lee Hills and Alvah Chapman, 1973; 10) Knight family gathering in Akron, includes Clara, JS & JL, 1938; 11) JS & JL in group of men, around table, at a Knight newspapers board meeting. Also includes copies of these and other Knight brother photos duplicated in very high resolution on cd.
      - Knight, John S., undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Knight, John S., undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
        Knight File Number - 2478
        Three copies of a black and white photograph of an etching of John S. Knight in profile. Knight is about 75 in the etching.
      - Knight, John S., 1890-1980 (Box 1, Folder 4)
        Knight File Number - 2291
        Sixteen b&w photos of John S. Knight: 1) JS as toddler, in dress; 2) JS as young boy, playing in snow, with dog; 3/4) JS in suit as young boy; 5) JS in group picture of football team (first row, left) - High School State Champions, 1913; 6) JS (in broad-brimmed hat) on boat trip with friends; 7) JS, WWII; 8) John S. Knight, Jr. in WWII uniform; 9) JS and Beryl Knight in winners' circle, Gulfstream Park, with race horse, 3/25/1961?; 10) JS with Tina Hills, 12/1964; 11) JS dancing with Mary Ann Knight, 12/1964; 12) JS with Tina Hills, Rad Crane, family, at Indian Creek Club, 12/1979; 13) JS Knight III as toddler; 14) JS's children at a young age; 15) JSK children, 1938; 16) JS and JSKIII
      - Knight, John S., 1940-1980 June (Box 1, Folder 5-6)
        Knight File Number - 933
        Several informal photographs of John S. Knight, JSK at his Underwood typewriter, with Blake McDowell, etc. (ca. 1940s); with Richard Nixon, receiving an honorary degree, etc. (ca. 1950s); on the cover of Newsweek (4/25/1955); with Jackie Gleason and Miami Herald events (1960s); portraits and an image of his Pulitzer Prize certificate (1968). Also a portrait (1970s, Akron Beacon Journal, black & white), a color portrait of Mr. Knight with his brother James (1970s, Miami Herald photo by Battle Vaughn), and an image of JSK speaking at an unidentified event at the Herald-Leader (ca. 1980, Creed Black, Alvah Chapman, and Bernard Ridder are seated in the background). There also is one color transparency of JSK with an unidentified couple. (two folders)
      - Knight, John S., c. 1970 (Box 1, Folder 6)
        Knight File Number - 4067
        Black and white portrait of John S. Knight, c. 1970. Donated by Tina Hills (removed from frame).
      - Knight, John S. with John F. Kennedy, Lee Hills at IAPA Event, 1963 November (Box 1, Folder 7)
        Knight File Number - 2292
        Three b&w photos of President John F. Kennedy, taken at an Inter-American Press Association (IAPA) event four days before JFK's assassination: 1) JS with JFK; 2) JFK with JS, Lee Hills, and Beryl Knight; Lee Hills and JFK.
      - Knight, John S. with Beryl Zoller Knight, 1947-1970 (Box 1, Folder 8)
        Knight File Number - 2293
        Three b&w photos of John S. Knight with his second wife, Beryl Zoller Knight: 1) at the University Club, in a crowd, c. 1947-49; 2) JS and Beryl sitting at a table; 3) JS and Beryl in box seats at race track.
      - Knight, John S. with Betty Augustus Knight, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 9)
        Knight File Number - 2294
        Two b&w photos of John S. Knight and his third wife, Elizabeth (Betty) Augustus Knight, undated but probably 1970s: 1) seated; 2) cutting cake at celebration of 85th anniversary of Akron Beacon Journal.
      - Knight, John S., Jr., 1941 (Box 1, Folder 10)
        Knight File Number - 2734
        Three b&w photos (all the same) of John S. Knight, Jr. as a prep-school boxer. The photos were donated by J. Barnett Woodruff, former classmate.
      - Knight, James L., undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
        Knight File Number - 2477
        Three copies of a black and white photograph of an etching of James L. Knight in profile. Knight is about 60 in the etching.
      - Knight, James L., 1929-1958 (Box 1, Folder 11)
        Knight File Number - 2285
        Eleven b&w photos of James L. Knight, personal photos and with family members: 1) a young JL with friend c. 1929; 2) JL with daughter Barbara, 1939; 3) JL and wife, Mary Ann, saving a sea turtle, 1940s; 4/5) JL and daughter Marjorie with sailboat, c. 1940s; 6) JL & Mary Ann, with daughters Marilyn (Deedee) and Barbara, c. 1940s; 7) JL & Mary Ann fishing with daughters Marilyn, Barbara and Marjorie, 1954; 8) JL and Mary Ann at debutante ball with daughter Barbara, 1955; 9) Mary Ann skeet shooting, c. 1950s; 10/11) JL fishing, 1958
      - Knight, James L., 1969 August 14-1979 December 31 (Box 1, Folder 12)
        Knight File Number - 932
        Photographs of James L. Knight, including photos by Battle Vaughan (Miami Herald staff photo), by Tony Spina (Detroit Free Press, 8/14/1969), and of JLK with Danny Martin and Creed Black by E. Martin Jessee (Herald Leader). Also includes images of JLK as a young man, a portrait (ca. 1960s) and with Lee Hills, C.C. Gibson and Blake McDowell (ca. 1970s). Black & white prints and one color transparency.
      - Knight, James L., 1960-1979 (Box 1, Folder 13)
        Knight File Number - 2286
        Twenty-one b&w photos, most personal, of James L. Knight, and family: 1) JL, Mary Ann and daughters Beverly and Marjorie, c. 1960; 2/3) JL with daughter, Marjorie K. Crane and with Mary Ann, and Marjorie and Alpo Crane on their wedding day, 12/18/1964; 4) JL (in black tie) & Mary Ann; 5) JL and Mary Ann with Marjorie Crane (holding daughter Michelle), Beverly and Mr. and Mrs. Crane; 6) JL with granson, Christopher "Kitt" Toomey, 12/1964; 7/8) JL with grandsons Kenny North and Jim Toomey, 12/1966; 9) JL's daughters on Beverly's wedding day: Marilyn, Barbara, Beverly, Marjorie; 10) JL with golfing buddies; 11/12) JL fishing in the Florida keys, 1970; 13) JL with family in Charlotte, NC, with Reed Toomey, Marilyn North, Marjorie Crane, Mary Ann, Barbara Toomey and Beverly Olson; 14) JL salmon fishing with friend, 1970; 15/16) JL at reception at Finnish Embassy, Washington DC, where he received a medal, with daughter Marjorie, and with Mary Ann and the Finnish ambassador, 6/1970; 17) JL holding chicken; 18/19) JL and Mary Ann with Crane grandchildren, c. 1976; 20) JL with Crane grandchildren, 1978; 21) JL with Lee Hills and Marjorie and other family members and friends celebrating Christmas at Indian Creek Club, 1979.
      - Knight, James L. - Retirement Party, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 14)
        Knight File Number - 2288
        Four b&w photos of JL at his Miami Herald retirement dinner, 1976: 1) JL (holding bird in cage), Mary Ann with daughters and sons-in-law; 2/3) JL, Mary Ann and daughters; 4) JL and Mary Ann (hidden) with daughters and sons-in-law (Beverly at lectern)
      - Knight, James L. - 40th Wedding Anniversary, circa 1970 (Box 1, Folder 15)
        Knight File Number - 2287
        Four b&w photos of JL and Mary Ann, with family and friends at their 40th Wedding Anniversary celebration, c. 1970s: 1) JL and Mary Ann seated at a table (Lee Hills in background); 2) JL, with Jim Carmine and Rad Crane (father of JL's son-in-law); 3) Marjorie and Beverly; 4) Marjorie, Mary Ann and Beverly.
      - Knight, James L., 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 16)
        Knight File Number - 2290
        Two b&w photos of JL and Mary Ann: 1) at ground-breaking ceremony for the Mary Ann and James L. Knight Nuclear Magnetic Resonance Imaging Center at Mount Sinai Medical Center, c. 1984; with Beverly and her son Charles, c. 1984/5
    - People - Other, 1989-1995; 4
      - Friday, William, 1994 February 24 (Box 1, Folder 31)
        Knight File Number - 922
        Photographs of Willliam Friday, Chairman of the Knight Commission on Intercollegiate Athletics, including photographs of Mr. Friday and Creed Black at the University of North Carolina, Distinguished Professorship Dinner (Mr. Friday spoke at the event). Black & white.
      - Gross, Lori, 1995 June (Box 1, Folder 33)
        Knight File Number - 925
        Photograph of Lori Gross, Project Manager of the Museum Art Loan Project, about 1995. Black & white.
      - Morris, Christopher B. (Kit), 1989 (Box 1, Folder 34)
        Knight File Number - 2524
        One b&w photograph of Christopher B. (Kit) Morris, who was appointed staff director of the Knight Commission on Intercollegiate Athletics in 1989.
    - Staff, 1982-2019; 5
      - Adams, Robertson G. (Robbie), 2002 (Box 1, Folder 1)
        Knight File Number - 2812
        Color portrait of Robbie Adams, communications associate - webmaster, 2002 -- (4 copies).
      - Anderson-Nearn, Sharon, circa 1991 (Box 1, Folder 2)
        Knight File Number - 912
        Photograph of Sharon Anderson-Nearn, Cities Program Officer, 1990. Black & white.
      - Bare, John, 1997-2002 (Box 1, Folder 3)
        Knight File Number - 2813
        Color portraits of John Bare, Director of Evaluation (1997-2004) (4 copies/ I negative).
      - Barraclough, Thor, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 4)
        Knight File Number - 2814
        B/w portrait of Thor Barraclough, communications associate - webmaster, 2001-2002 (2 copies).
      - Bernstein, Judith, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 5)
        Knight File Number - 2815
        B/w portrait of Judith Bernstein, communications assistant (2 copies).
      - Black, Creed C., 1982 December 30-1998 March 16 (Box 1, Folder 6-8)
        Knight File Number - 915
        Formal and informal photographs (black & white, color, and negatives) of Creed C. Black, KF President (1987-1998), including images at speaking engagements, a Knight Commission event, with Elizabeth Dole, Ross Perot, Elsa (his wife), and others (three folders). Also includes three contact sheets of photographs taken at his retirement dinner in March, 1998.
      - Brinkman, Del, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 9)
        Knight File Number - 2816
        B/w and color portrait of Del Brinkman, Journalism Program Officer, 1993 - 2001 (2 copies each).
      - Brooks, Julie, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 10)
        Knight File Number - 2817
        Color portrait of Julie Brooks, Grants Administrator, 2002 -- (4 copies).
      - Bumpus, Tyrone, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 11)
        Knight File Number - 2818
        Color portrait of Tyrone Bumpus, IT Technical Support Specialist, 2000 -- 2004 (2 copies).
      - Burger, Gary, 1997-2002 (Box 1, Folder 12)
        Knight File Number - 2819
        Color and b/w portraits of Gary Burger, Arts & Culture Program Officer, 1997-2002 (2 copies of each).
      - Carter, Hodding, 1995 June-2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
        Knight File Number - 917
        Photographs of Hodding Carter III, holder of the Knight Chair at the University of Maryland, 1995. Also portraits of Carter as President, CEO and trustee of KF, 1997 - 2003 and undated, including Hodding with staff and at informal events. Black & white and color, including some negatives and a cd.
      - Carter, Hodding - Fodder for Hodding Memento, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Clossick, Beatriz (Betty), 2000 (Box 1, Folder 14)
        Knight File Number - 2820
        Color and b/w portrait of Betty Clossick, VP of Accounting and Treasurer, 2000 - 2004 (3 copies).
      - Colon, Yves, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 15)
        Knight File Number - 2821
        Color portrait of Yves Colon, Journalism Program Officer, 2001-2003 (3 copies).
      - Coudreaut, Terese, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 16)
        Knight File Number - 2822
        Color portrait of Terese Coudreaut, Workforce Performance and Development Manager, 2002 -- (4 copies).
      - Crowe, Timothy J., 1997-2002 (Box 1, Folder 17)
        Knight File Number - 2823
        Several color and b/w portraits of Tim Crowe, VP and Chief Investment Officer, 1990-2005 (8 copies and 1 neg).
      - Cruz, Alfredo, c. 2002 (Box 1, Folder 18)
        Knight File Number - 2824
        Color negatives of Alfredo Cruz, Community Liaison Program Officer, 1995 -- (3 copies).
      - Diaz. Raul A., c. 2002 (Box 1, Folder 19)
        Knight File Number - 2825
        Color amd b/w portraits of Raul Diaz, Director of Investment, 1999-2006 (4 items).
      - Ervin, Joe L., 2002 (Box 1, Folder 20)
        Knight File Number - 2826
        Color portrait of Joe Ervin, Director of Community Partners Program (4 copies).
      - Francis, Philip C., 2002 (Box 1, Folder 21)
        Knight File Number - 2827
        Color portrait of Philip Francis, ITAssociate/ Web Technician, 2002 - 2006 (3 copies).
      - Gomez, Susan, 2000-2002 (Box 1, Folder 22)
        Knight File Number - 2828
        Color portraits of Susan Gomez, Office Manager, 2000 -- (4 items).
      - Grossman, Kathryn, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 23)
        Knight File Number - 2829
        Color portrait of Katie Grossman, Investment Assistant, 2002-2006 (3 copies).
      - Harnish, Steven G., 2001 (Box 1, Folder 24)
        Knight File Number - 2830
        Color portrait of Steven Harnish, Investment Associate, 2001-2002 (1 copy).
      - Hector, Meredith Maust, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 25)
        Knight File Number - 2831
        Color portrait of Meredith Maust Hector, Executive Secretary to Chief Program Officer, 2002 -- (1 copy).
      - Henke, Virginia, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 26)
        Knight File Number - 928
        Photograph of Virginia Henke, Communications Director, about 1990. Black & white.
      - Ibarguen, Alberto - Speech in Myrtle Beach, SC - Thumbnail Prints, 2005 August 11 (Box 1, Folder 27)
        Knight File Number - 4558
        Photos of Alberto Ibarguen giving a speech and meeting with participants at a press conference in Myrtle Beach launching the Knight Step-Up Project.
      - Ibarguen, Alberto - Speech in Myrtle Beach, SC - Knight Press Conference, 2005 August 11 (Box 1, Folder 27)
        Digital photos of Alberto Ibarguen giving a speech and meeting with participants at a press conference in Myrtle Beach launching the Knight Step-Up Project.
      - Ibarguen, Alberto - Speech in Myrtle Beach, SC - Knight Step-Up Photos, Randall Hill (Box 1, Folder 27)
      - Ibarguen, Alberto - Red Cross Honors - Thumbnail Prints, 2005 December 5 (Box 1, Folder 28)
        Knight File Number - 4557
        Photos of Alberto Ibarguen receiving an honor from the Red Cross in his office in Miami. Mike Maidenberg is in some of the pictures.
      - Ibarguen, Alberto - Red Cross Honors, 2005 December 5 (Box 1, Folder 28)
        Digital photos of Alberto Ibarguen receiving an honor from the Red Cross in his office in Miami. Mike Maidenberg is in some of the pictures.
      - Ibarguen, Alberto - Knight-Batten Innovation Awards & University of Maryland Presentation - Thumbnail Prints, 2006 September 18 (Box 1, Folder 29)
        Knight File Number - 4559
        Photos of Alberto Ibarguen giving a speech at the ceremony for the Knight-Batten awards and receiving a plaque at the Knight Hall of the University of Maryland.
      - Ibarguen, Alberto - Knight-Batten Innovation Awards & University of Maryland Presentation, 2006 September 18 (Box 1, Folder 29)
        Digital photos of Alberto Ibarguen giving a speech at the ceremony for the Knight-Batten awards and receiving a plaque at the Knight Hall of the University of Maryland.
      - Ibarguen, Alberto - Portraits High Resolution (1028, 1006, 1023, 1015), 2009 November 6 (Box 1, Folder 29)
        Knight File Number - 4763
        Digital portraits of Alberto Ibarguen.
      - Ibarguen, Alberto - Portraits High Resolution (1031), 2009 November 6 (Box 1, Folder 29)
      - Ibarguen, Alberto - White House, 2014 March 5 (Box 1, Folder 30)
        Knight File Number - 5305
        Color copy of photograph sent from the White House of Alberto and Susana Ibarguen in front of a portrait of Abraham Lincoln. They were attending a Women of Soul concert which will be broadcast on PBS April 7, 2014.
      - Alberto Ibarguen - Portraits, 2015-2019 (Box 1, Folder 31)
        Knight File Number - 5632
        Restricted - Open 2030
        Color copy of photographs of Alberto Ibarguen - a full-length portrait, Alberto at a lectern, and Alberto with Bahia Ramos and Susan Patterson at her retirement party. Alberto Ibarguen with Dr. Gerald Austen, former trustee, during a taped interview in Boston, July 26, 2019
      - Kaiser, Beth J., 2001 (Box 1, Folder 32)
        Knight File Number - 2832
        Color portrait of Beth Kaiser, Investment Associate, 2001-2003 (2 copies).
      - Kebbel, Gary, 2006-2010 (Box 1, Folder 33)
        Knight File Number - 4551
        Color portraits of Gary Kebbel, Journalism Program Officer. Also includes 2 copies of an informal color portrait of Gary wearing a Nebraska t-shirt. Gary left KF to assume a position at the University of Nebraska.
      - Kevers, Robert, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 34)
        Knight File Number - 2523
        Two portraits (b&w, 5"x7) of Knight Foundation controller, Robert Kever.
      - Kohler, Julie, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 35)
        Knight File Number - 2833
        Color portrait of Julie Kohler, Content Program Officer, 2002 -- (3 copies).
      - Lawrence, Belinda Turner, 1997-2012 (Box 1, Folder 36)
        Knight File Number - 2834